http://www.legalfunding.com/company/privacy_policy.cfm

RD Legal Funding, LLC Email and Online Privacy Policy
RD Legal Funding, LLC ("RD Legal") is sensitive to the privacy of those that visit this Web site and is committed to respecting your online privacy. We recognize the need for appropriate protections and management of your Personal Information that is provided to us via this Web site. You can travel through most of this Web site without giving us any personally identifiable information about yourself.
This Web site is owned and controlled by RD Legal Funding, LLC, 45 Legion Drive, 2nd Floor, Cresskill, NJ, 07626, USA. By accessing this Web site, you acknowledge the terms and conditions set forth herein. We reserve the right to change these policies from time to time, without notice and at our sole discretion, but we will not use or share any personally identifiable information provided to us prior to any such change in ways other than the ones described herein without first letting you know and offering you a choice to withhold your permission for such intended use.
Online privacy is a constantly evolving landscape and we plan to take all reasonable efforts to maintain up-to-date and effective online privacy standards and practices. We have linked every page of our Web site to this page for your convenience and you may also contact us with any questions or concerns that you may have.
Sometimes, however, we do need information to provide services that you request, and RD Legal has established this Email and Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand what information we collect, and the care with which we intend to treat the Personal Information that you provide.
1) If you received an email, why did you receive a mailing from us?
Our email marketing is based on publically available information derived from sources such as state bar records and court filings. Alternately, you may have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt in"), or you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us.
Each email contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the unsubscribe or update profile links at the end of any email.
2) What personally identifiable information
do we at RD Legal collect from you?
We collect Personal Information from our users at several different points on this Web site. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, a company name, a telephone number, an email address or other contact information, whether at home or at work. RD Legal does collect personally identifiable financial information on our on-line application.
In general, you can visit the RD Legal Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. Sometimes, however, we will require or request you to provide Personal Information. Generally this information is requested when you are asked for one or more of the following: 1) filling out a sales information request or contact form; 2) becoming a registered user; 3) signing up for a mailing list; 4) during correspondence with us; 5) completing a survey that we use for research, and 6) any other such activities as we deem appropriate. Occasionally, we may use this information when we notify you about important changes to our Web site.
You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests Personal Information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, you may not be able to complete the applicable transaction.
We strive to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, we intend to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require a level of protection for your Personal Information that is of a standard comparable to the principles set forth here. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information in accordance with the principles that are set forth in this Online Privacy Policy no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred or retained.
3) How does RD Legal collect information and
how will we use such information?
RD Legal is the owner of the information collected on this Web site. We will not sell, share, trade or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Online Privacy Policy without first letting you know and offering you a choice to withhold your permission for such intended use. We collect information from several points on this Web site.
When we capture information about your session or about you, we may use it for research or to improve our Web site and the services we offer you. We will ask you if you want us to use the information you provide to continue contact with you. The mediums in which we may contact you include but are not limited to email, telephone, or postal mail (for example, to send you information or special offers, or for other marketing purposes).
Additionally, we will use information to assist us in creating content that is relevant to you, to assist us in creating better products and services to meet your needs, to provide you with access to services or otherwise engage in activities you select, and to help you quickly find software, services, or product information important to you.
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on our Web site, we may transfer that information, within RD Legal or to our affiliates, business partners or third party service providers, across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world
4) What are cookies and how does RD Legal use them?
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. "Cookies" are small text files placed on your computer's hard drive that are read by the server that placed them, are unable to execute any code or virus and cannot take any additional information from your hard drive. These cookies allow our Web site to recognize you when you revisit the site, and are able to remember certain information about you, such as your preferences in the site and the type of content you find of interest so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site.
Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. Generally, you can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. If you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of our Web site.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics
5) Links to other Web sites and Third Parties.
This Web site may contain links to other sites on the Internet, which are owned and operated by our partners, customers and other third parties. We have not reviewed and will not review these Web sites, which are linked to the RD Legal Web site. We have no control over such external sites, do not endorse any external sites and are not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials that may appear on or may be available on, from or through any such external site. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site or click on a link to another site from our site, that they should read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites or any other Web sites that are linked to our site that may collect personally identifiable information about you. The data collection practices of those Web sites are not covered by RD Legal Privacy Policy.
6) With whom is information shared?
We do not sell, trade, or rent your Personal Information to others, except as specified in this Privacy Policy. When you are at our site and are asked for Personal Information, you are sharing that information only with RD Legal and its affiliates, business partners and third party service providers unless otherwise specifically stated. We may offer a service or promotion in conjunction with business partners, for example, a joint seminar or a product integration solution. In cases such as these, information collected may be shared by both companies.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact and billing information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. We are not responsible for, nor do we have any liability in connection with the control or use of the information by such third parties.
The other circumstance under which RD Legal may disclose your Personal Information to another party is when legally required to do so or when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires such a disclosure. For example, we will share such information if we have reason to believe that the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be either causing injury to or interference with RD Legal's rights or property, or RD Legal's customers or affiliates.
7) What options do you have regarding collection, use, distribution and change of your information?
If you provide us with your email or postal address, or have done so in the past, we may use it to send you information on the latest RD Legal products, promotions, and events. We may use information you have given to us, for example, to measure consumer interest in our various products, or to inform you about new products and services. These offers may be based on information you provided in your initial transaction with us or in surveys. RD Legal provides an easy means to decline to receive such email offers. All email offers that you receive from RD Legal will tell you how to decline further email offers. To manually unsubscribe from our email lists, please reply to our email and type in "unsubscribe" in the subject. If Personal Information is received from you through our Web site, our goal is to provide a means of contacting RD Legal if you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may contact us with updates and corrections about your Personal Information and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.
8) Children's Privacy.
The Web sites of RD Legal are not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone that we know to be under 13 years of age.
9) What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?
To protect the privacy of any Personal Information you may have provided, we employ a number of industry-recognized controls including physical access controls, Internet firewalls, intrusion detection, and network monitoring. Additionally, only authorized administrators and staff have access to systems containing such information. Backup data are securely stored and not shared with third parties.
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us. Although we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.
10) Your Consent.
By using the RD Legal Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy regarding the use and processing of Personal Information and any other terms that may be set forth on our Web site where RD Legal collects Personal Information.
Apply Now for your free legal funding consultation
- select funding type -
Attorney Funding
Plaintiff Funding
all fields required
Memberships & Partnerships:
"As a personal injury attorney, I can be facing up to $5 million in expenses for a single case - expenses that can't be written off on taxes. RD Legal Funding makes it possible for me to have consistent cash flow."
Gerald J. Diaz
Diaz Law Firm, Madison, Mississippi
RD Legal Funding, LLC
45 Legion Drive
Cresskill, NJ 07626
P: 1-800-565-5177
Home
About
